A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Log Files (Grant and Project Proposals) FA734
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1979
  - L79-192: The Studio Museum in Harlem: Support for the museum's search for permanent residence, 1979 (Reel L-416)
  - L79-193: Georgetown University: Middle East Sci-Tech Information Service and Exchange, 1979 (Reel L-416)
  - L79-194: American Council on Education, Washington, DC: Special Projects, 1979 (Reel L-416)
  - L79-195: Ford Foundation: Arab-Israeli conciliation efforts, 1979 (Reel L-416)
  - L79-196: Ford Foundation: Support of participants in Bhagwati-Chelliah tax seminar, 1979 (Reel L-416)
  - L79-197: University of Washington, Seattle: Support project to evaluate retention capacity of minority students, 1979 (Reel L-416)
  - L79-199: Ford Foundation: Funds for conference for Palestinian and American educators at Harvard University, 1979 (Reel L-416)
  - L79-200: Ford Foundation: United States Agency for International Development Regional Cooperation program, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-201: Ford Foundation: Funds for guide lines for staff development of African teachers in elementary schools of South Africa, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-204: Population Resource Center, NYC: Aspen Institute conference on population redistribution on Egypt, 1979 (Reel L-419)
  - L79-207: Indiana University: Arab integration research projects, 1979 (Reel L-419)
  - L79-208: University of Nigeria: Agricultural training Proposal, 1979 (Reel L-419)
  - L79-211: Ford Foundation: Study of Middle East Centers at U.S. Universities, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-217: Ford Foundation: Administration of urban blacks in South Africa, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-219: Shaw College, Detroit: Special Project fund for Michigan, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-224: Ford Foundation: Media and law in Israel, 1979 (Reel L-520)
  - L79-226: University of Wisconsin: Support a training program in resource economics, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-227: Caribbean Human Rights and Legal Aid Co., Trinidad: Funds to meet cost of documentary and publishing results of a seminar, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-228: Ford Foundation: International Security and Arms Control in Middle East and Africa, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-230: Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges: Increasing effectiveness of trustees at Black Colleges, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-231: University of Californa: Project comparing Japanese and German economic expansion, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-233: New York City Uiversity of Graduate School Center: To encourage students to pursue German at the Graduate Level, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-235: Ford Foundation: General support - Southern Sudan, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-237: University of Minnesota: Study international trial observance, 1979 (Reel L-419)
  - L79-238: National Council for Civil Liberties: Joint project on the European Convention, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-239: Social Science Research Council: African Bourgeoisie International Conference, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-240: Gadjah Mada University, Indonesia: Development of an Environmental Management Research and Training Program, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-243: Ford Foundation: Economic policy analysis and productivity, 1979 (Reel L-419)
  - L79-244: University of Wisconsin: National Study of the Teaching of Education Law, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-246: Ford Foundation: Pakistan program review, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-247: Ford Foundation: Commonwealth Program for applied studies in Government, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-248: Ford Foundation: U.S./ India Bilateral International Security Conference, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-249: Institution of Development Studies, England: Political economy of Information in the North-South Negotiating Process, 1979 (Reel L-419)
  - L79-250: Ford Foundation: Information re: International Monetary System, 1979 (Reel L-419)
  - L79-251: Chulalongkorn University: Seminar for Vietnamese and other regional scholars to discuss recent developments in Vietnam, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-257: Ford Foundation: Canadian studies, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-258: Washington Center of Foreign Policy Research, D.C.: Support for new magazine on the Soviet Union, 1979 (Reel L-419)
  - L79-259: International Council for Adult Education: Adult education strategies in primary health care programs, 1979 (Reel L-419)
  - L79-261: Woodrow Wilson Center: Security Studies program, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-262: International Commission of Jurists, Switzerland: Human rights, 1979 (Reel L-419)
  - L79-264: Center for Strategic International Studies, Georgetown University: Proposal: Arabs in Africa -the Security Dimension, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-265: Ford Foundation: Explore employment expansion in south Asian agriculture, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-266: Ford Foundation: Information on Soviet Union and Asia, 1979 (Reel L-417)
  - L79-270: Ford Foundation: Central America General Information Log, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-271: Ford Foundation: African Refugees, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-272: Bangladesh Rural Advancement Committee: Cold Storage Project / Food, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-273: American Association for the Advancement of Science, Washington, DC: Women and Science and Math Support, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-276: American Friends Service Committee: Pilot programs on refugees, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-278: Ford Foundation: Computers in schools, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-282: Community Economic Organization, Kingston, Jamaica: Seminars consultant and training in employment generation and community development, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-284: Ford Foundation: Information log on resources and the environment in the developing countries, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-287: American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Boston, MA: Proposal on Iran, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-289: Ford Foundation: To review the Foundation's recent work in education to develop future program directions, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-290: Ford Foundation: International conference on the 2nd economy, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-294: Ford Foundation: Development of social sciences in the Philippines, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-300: Federal University of Paraiba: Research support for programs of agricultural economics and rural sociology, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-302: The Ohio State University: The Concept of Public Education: Past, Present and Future a National Symposium, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-303: Duke University: Reading skills research, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-305: Georgetown University, Washington, DC: Development of the Institute for the study of diplomacy, 1979 (Reel L-419)
  - L79-306: American Society of International Law, Washington, DC: Legal and institutional aspects of U.S. policy options toward Southern Africa, 1979 (Reel L-418)
  - L79-308: National Science Foundation: International economic policy program, 1979 (Reel L-419)
  - L79-309: Center for Policy Research, New Delhi, India: General support of the programs of the Center, 1979 (Reel L-419)
- 1980
  - L80-1: Ford Foundation: UN Mid Decade Conference, 1980 (Reel L-433)
  - L80-3: Ford Foundation: Information Log on Women's Program, 1980 (Reel L-433)
  - L80-5: Ford Foundation: International Conference on the Stabilization policy of the International Monetary Fund, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-8: International African Institute: Language Planning, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-10: American University in Cairo (AUC): Family planning, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-12: Ford Foundation: Future course of Ford Foundation involvement in fields of prehistory archaeology and museology in Southereast Asia, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-13: Ford Foundation: Women and development in the Andes and Southern Cone, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-14: Harvard University: Sudi American Relations, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-17: Mary Ingamham Bunting Institute of Radcliffe College: International Scholars Program for research on women and work, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-18: Ford Foundation: Rural social science consortium for Africa, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-20: Ford Foundation: Program development, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-24: Ford Foundation: Agricultural economic, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-25: Ford Foundation: Information log on International Security and Arms control in India, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-28: University of Khartoum: General Information, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-29: British Council of Churches: Council on Christian Approaches to defense and disarmament, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-30: Ford Foundation: Tradition Islamic education in contemporary cultural contexts, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-33: Ford Foundation: Project in nutrition and food policy in Mexico, and central America, 1980 (Reel L-434)
  - L80-34: International Foundation of Human Sciences: Project on the future roles of the welfare State, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-36: Ford Foundation: West Bank Agriculture, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-38: Ford Foundation: Support for production of a documentary on the Polisario movement in Western Sahara, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-40: Ford Foundation: Study on U.S. economic assistance to Africa, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-42: CASS Research Associates: General information log, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-43: Ford Foundation: Euro Commission Materials, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-44: International Documentation and Communications Center: 1)Student Handbook 2)cost on documentation 3)documentation project on transnational corporations, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-47: The University of New Mexico: Support to develop an information center on native American in Higher Education, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-48: Agricultural Development Council: General support, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-52: Colegio Cesar Chavez.: Support for institutional development, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-56: Ford Foundation: Womens programs in Brazil, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-58: Ford Foundation: Community based water management in India and Philippines, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-60: Ford Foundation: Study and management of changing economic systems in Egypt's western desert, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-62: Federation for American Immigration Reform: Financing for work directed towards reform of immigration policy and law, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-63: University of Maryland: Refugees: Assessing the U.S. share of the global burden, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-65: York University: Canadian study of Indo-Chinese Refugees, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-67: Cornell University: To plan a minority and mathematics project, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-68: American Jewish Committee: Background info log on American Jewish committee, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-72: Ford Foundation: Information file on abortion, 1980 (Reel L-435)
  - L80-73: Caribbean Central American Action: To enhance mutual awareness, appreciation and friendship between the people of the US and the people of Central America and the Caribbean, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-77: Ford Foundation: Latin American Culture Humanities Information Log, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-79: Preterm Institute, Inc: Support for Abortion Technology, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-81: Ford Foundation: Rights Education and Legal Services in Brazil, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-82: Ford Foundation: 2 Proposals - 1) Political changes in Poland in the 70's and 2) Methodology of Macro-Sociological Analysis, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-84: Ford Foundation: South Bronx Nutrition Project, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-85: Ford Foundation: International economic order: resources and the environment, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-86: Ford Foundation: Trustee paper on FF Resources Environment, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-87: Spelman College: Symposium on Minority women, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-88: Policy Studies Institute: Project on the use time budgets in Policy Analysis, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-89: Ford Foundation: Future work on the Arts Programs, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-90: Harvard University: Moving men concerning women, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-94: Wake Forest University: Adolescent underachievement and discipline, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-98: Regional Plan Association: Review current status of higher education in New York and help local colleges and Universities emerge economic, social and demographic trends, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-100: Atlanta University Center, Inc.: General Support, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-102: University of California: Support to carry a Multi Country study of the Political Economy of Food Prices, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-104: Systems Research Ltd.: What teachers think of students and schools: A comparative study, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-105: South African Institute of Race Relations: Urban Relocation, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-106: American Civil Liberties Union: General Information Log on Immigration, 1980 (Reel L-438)
  - L80-109: Ford Foundation: Information log on women, 1980 (Reel L-439)
  - L80-110: Teachers Corp: To develop a Professional Memory through the practice of Reflective Inquiry, 1980 (Reel L-439)
  - L80-113: Ford Foundation: Pakistan Agriculture, 1980 (Reel L-439)
  - L80-116: The Moving Image, Inc. (Film Forum): PRI construction loan to reconstruct and equip new facilities on Watts Street, New York City, 1980 (Reel L-439)
  - L80-119: Sarvodaya Shvamadama Movement: Research and development, 1980 (Reel L-439)
  - L80-120: Ford Foundation: Refugees and Migration, 1980 (Reel L-439)
  - L80-121: Ford Foundation: Social Forestry in the Philippine Uplands, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-122: National Abortions Rights League Foundation: Funding for their education project - Abortion, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-123: University Of Allahabad: Support for Program on International Security Studies, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-127: Ford Foundation: Research on development of Social Sciences in Africa and Middle East, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-129: Ford Foundation: Minorities in Science and Math, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-131: Ford Foundation: Women in Math and Science, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-134: Battelle Memorial Institute: Study of impact of return migration on Puerto Rican Society, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-136: Pacific News Service: Investigate Future for Children of Immigrants from the Southern Hemisphere, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-137: Ford Foundation: Internationalizing Public Policy, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-138: Case -Western Reserve University, Cleveland, Ohio: Study of Immigrant Absorption in the U.S., 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-139: Ford Foundation: Support for Public Service TV program, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-142: European Cultural Foundation: General Information log on the Foundation, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-143: US Chamber of Commerce: Information on International Service Industry Committee, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-144: Ford Foundation: Political development in Egypt and Turkey, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-153: Centre Intergroup Studies: Support for their Constructive Program, 1980 (Reel L-551)
  - L80-156: Ford Foundation: School Staff Development, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-159: University of California/Santa Cruz: Write a book on Creation and Development of Oaks College at the University of California/Santa Cruz, 1980 (Reel L-440)
  - L80-162: Resources for the Future, Inc.: General information on Resources for the Future, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-164: University of Southern California/College of Continuing Education: Regional Program on Women in Higher Education Administration, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-169: Ford Foundation: Share Holder resolutions, Latin America and the Caribbean, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-171: Ford Foundation: General Information on Adolescent Pregnancies, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-173: Pacific Forum: Support for Study to Examine Changing National Security Policies of a Number of East Asian Countries, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-175: University of California /Los Angeles: Survey on American Attitude towards Abortion, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-176: European Medical Research Council: General Information on Follow-on to the Greep Report, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-178: Ford Foundation: A P Agricultural Seminar 1981, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-180: Ford Foundation: International Conference -New Approaches to the worldwide refugee situation, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-181: University of Michigan /Ann Arbor: Evaluation of Family Planning Education in Michigan High Schools, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-185: Academy for Educational Development: To use IBM selectric in an Multi- Media system for teaching Kindergarten and 1st Grade Black Children to read, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-186: Vocational Education Reform Alliance: Improvement of a Vocational Education Opportunities for Teenage Girls, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-187: Ford Foundation: Proposed book on Janusz Korczak, 1980 (Reel L-441)
  - L80-189: Group of Thirty: Study of International Economic and Monetary Systems, 1980 (Reel L-442)
  - L80-192: Center for Cultural and Technical Interchange Between East and West, Inc: Project on the concept of equality in an inter-dependent world, 1980 (Reel L-442)
  - L80-193: Ford Foundation: Ruby d'Aschot-Correspondence on European and International Affairs, 1980 (Reel L-442)
  - L80-195: Ford Foundation: Papers on Refugee and Immigration Policy, 1980 (Reel L-442)
  - L80-197: Ford Foundation: 1981 Membership Dues to the Independent sector, 1980 (Reel L-442)
  - L80-199: American Friends Service Committee: A Public Education and Action Program for Americans on Immigration and Refugee Policy, 1980 (Reel L-442)
  - L80-200: American Center of Oriental Research: Cooperative Program with the University of Jordan, 1980 (Reel L-442)
  - L80-204: Kamehameha Schools: To study the Kamehameha early education program, 1980 (Reel L-442)
  - L80-207: Ford Foundation: General Information Log on Portugal, 1980 (Reel L-442)
  - L80-209: Organization for Social Science Research in Eastern Africa: Mexico - General Information Log (see PA82-1052), 1980 (Reel L-442)
  - L80-211: Ford Foundation: Information log -Brazil, 1980 (Reel L-442)
  - L80-212: Ford Foundation: Human Rights -Latin America and the Caribbean, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-213: Ford Foundation: Refugees, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-214: Ford Foundation: Dual -Expertise Fellowship Program Review, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-215: Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights (R.C.A.R.): To Generate Support for Abortion Rights at the Grass-Roots Level, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-216: Florida State University: Center for Studies of Women in Educational Management Systems: To Establish a Higher Education Resource Services Project, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-217: Coordinating Board of Indonesian Fertility Research: Training on Research Methodology, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-218: World Paper: General support, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-219: International Centre for Diarrheal Disease Research: Methodological Studies on Contraceptive Risk, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-220: Ford Foundation: Proposal on Mortality down, population up, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-223: Ford Foundation: Health and Nutrition, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-224: Asian-American Legal Defense and Education Fund: Support to Address Critical Problems in Asian-American Communities, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-226: Ford Foundation: 1980 Asia and Pacific Program Review (Reel L-443)
  - L80-227:: European Parliament - U.S. Congress Project (see PA81-859), 1980 (Reel L-551)
  - L80-229: Arizona Board of Regents Acting for and on Behalf of Arizona State University: Provide coherent job oriented academic curriculum for re-entry and transfer women, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-230: The Equity Policy Center: Efforts to ensure wide distribution of various journals concerning women studies, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-233: Ford Foundation: Life Stress and Neo-Natal Mortality, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-235: Martha Stuart Communications, Inc.: Village Network Project, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-238: Rutgers University Eagleton Institute of Politics: General Support, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-239: Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars: Support for study on dissidents and dissent in East European Politics, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-240: Human Rights Internet: African Human Rights, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-243: Committee for the Free World: Conferences on East-West Relations, 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-244: National Committee for Full Employment: Bi-weekly news service Jobs Impact Bulletin (see PA84-177), 1980 (Reel L-443)
  - L80-247: Atlantic Institute for International Affairs: General Information log on the Institute, 1980 (Reel L-443)
- 1981
  - L81-1: Ethiopian Aid: Assistance to Ethiopian refugees in the Sudan, 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-3: Ford Foundation: Vietnam, 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-4: Ford Foundation: Women in the military, 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-5: Ford Foundation: US and European response to economic and institutional challenges to the established international order., 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-6: University of Newcastle: Support for seminar in Europe, 1981 (Reel L-515)
  - L81-7: Americans for Middle East Understanding Inc.: General Information, 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-8: Kaplan Hospital: Impact of sex education on adolescents in Israel, 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-12: University of Michigan: Politics and consequences of the adolescent pregnancy initiative of 1978, 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-13: Hispanic Council on Foreign Affairs: Creation of a secretariat, 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-19: German Agency for Technical Cooperation: Establish foundation-like activities in the Philippines, 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-22: Georgetown University Institute for the Study of Diplomacy: Examine and teach basic techniques of diplomacy, 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-23: Ford Foundation: Development of Japan Program, 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-26: City University of New York, City College: Study of how immigrant Chinese garment workers adjust in New York's Chinatown, 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-29: Catholic University of Louvain: Perinatal mortality and characteristics of children at birth in Kinshasa, 1981 (Reel L-452)
  - L81-30: Ford Foundation: Study of poverty focused development in one region of Bangladesh, Indonesia, Pakistan and Ghana, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-37: Southern Women's Educational Alliance: High School Clearinghouse/Organizing Project, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-38: Ford Foundation: Tibet and international law: towards a solution, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-40: Ford Foundation: Confidence in the public schools, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-42: International Rice Research Institute: Irrigation /water management network, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-43: Ford Foundation: Intermediate Support Organizations - Rural poverty and resources - Mexico, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-45: Charles F. Kettering Foundation: Conference to explore public policy in international affairs program, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-50: African Fellowships for Graduate Research and Development (NYC): Enable more African women to pursue graduate study in the United States, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-51: Yale University: Rhesus Reproduction: Data from the Van Wagenen Colony, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-52: Ford Foundation: General information log on the Andies and Southern Cone, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-54: Foreign Policy Research Institute: Conference on security in South/West Asia, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-55: Chulalongkorn University: Seminar on Asian Energy and Security, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-57: American Jewish Congress, Inc.: An American/Israeli/Egyptian Dialogue, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-59: National Council of Returned Peace Corps Volunteers: To educate Americans about the developing countries and the interdependent world, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-60: Fullbright Alumni Association: General support, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-62: Ford Foundation: General information log on the Caribbean, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-64: Ford Foundation: Asian and African Agricultural Research, 1981 (Reel L-453)